Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy applies to all available browser extension products (Speed Dial, Eco Search) that are offerd by our company.

The protection and security of personal data has a high priority. Below you will be informed about the type of data collected and the purpose for which it is collected.

**Scope of processing of personal data**

We only process personal data of our users if this is necessary to provide a functional service. The processing of personal data of our users takes place regularly only after consent of the user. An exception applies in those cases where prior consent cannot be obtained for real reasons and the processing of the data is permitted by law.

**Legal basis for processing personal data**

Insofar as we obtain the consent of the data subject for the processing of personal data, Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) serves as the legal basis. In the processing of personal data required for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is a party, Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR serves as the legal basis. This also applies to processing operations that are necessary to carry out pre-contractual measures. Insofar as the processing of personal data is required to fulfil a legal obligation to which our company is subject, Art. 6 para. 1 lit. c GDPR serves as the legal basis. In the event that the vital interests of the data subject or another natural person require the processing of personal data, Article 6(1)(d) GDPR serves as the legal basis. If processing is necessary to safeguard a legitimate interest of our company or a third party and if the interests, fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject do not outweigh the first-mentioned interest, Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR serves as the legal basis for processing.

**Data erasure and storage time**

The personal data of the person concerned will be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose of storage ceases to apply. Furthermore, data may be stored if this has been provided for by the European or national legislator in EU regulations, laws or other provisions to which the person responsible is subject. The data will also be blocked or deleted if a storage period prescribed by the aforementioned standards expires, unless there is a need for further storage of the data for the conclusion or fulfilment of a contract.

**Data transfer and data logging**

When you visit this page or use a servcies provided by AddonSearch.net, the web server automatically registers log files that cannot be assigned to a specific person. These data include the requested target page URL, browser type and version, operating system used, referrer URL, IP address of the requesting computer, date and time of the request. This data is only stored for the purpose of statistical evaluation and to ensure system security. A passing on to third parties is not carried out, unless a passing on is necessary due to legal regulations.

**Right of information, modification and deletion**

In accordance with applicable law, you can ask us at any time whether and what personal data about you is stored by us. You will be notified immediately.

**External content**

External content from Google can be used (e.g. Google Fonts). Such external content can be embedded in the web page and therefore send the IP address to the respective service when called for technical reasons.

**Search results**

For a search query the following data may be used on third party search result pages: user agent, IP address, page URL, anonymous user identification or any other data that is used in connection with the search serving and quality systems. This information is provided at the time a query is sent to the third party search service (Yahoo, Bing). The legal basis is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR, as we have a legitimate interest in serving suitable search results for the user.

Additional policy for "Eco Search" extension: Some of the web search services provided herein are provided by find.searchfuel.co Search and powered by find.searchfuel.co search partners. For information on the web search services data collection, please visit [http://info.searchfuel.co/](http://info.searchfuel.co/), and the search provider's privacy policy, as applicable.
